i'm home grandpa and i'm with him so that's it shopping's all done yep also the mannequin i
ordered should be here later today for real i'm super excited gojo check it out how does this look
dude that was so freaking loud what's the deal you're showing me your underwear that's the deal
first of all no it's the swimsuit i bought earlier today remember the time we were texting about the
outfit and i sent you a swimsuit selfie and you left me on red that was brave son and way rude
uh i uh a lot happened after i saw that photo anyway there was so much drama trying to find
the high-waisted ones i finally had to go the imported route nice huh something wrong look i'm
i'm sorry could you just uh leave me alone for a bit
oh yeah you want me to leave and why is that she wondered aw is someone a bit too excited at the
moment i'm fine really and the swimsuit is great you just absolutely cannot touch me right now okay
whoa are you mad like mad mad no i'm not i'm just suddenly in need of some personal space
this is totally random but do you ever find yourself blowing on cold food like it's hot
sometimes and then you're like totally embarrassed once you realize it okay now that is some genius
art i'm so happy yeah that's quite a smile i think my face is gonna break i was useful i can't tell you
how incredible just saying that feels don't judge me i know it's a bit extra to get all emo over some
paint but wow
maybe today i was actually useful
it's so freaking pretty i'm even more hyped for this cosplay now i can't help it i need to try it on
no stick out my way oh it's fine we're bros
no not happening just let me know when you're done
you can look i don't care i actually have a cute brawl on today check it
crap this is not the one i thought i was wearing
up
do you help it or don't you
see me
me
sick
Thank you.
Is it comfortable enough?
Yeah, it's perfect.
Good, that's important. You want to change anything?
Maybe. I'm pretty sure that the skirt design is supposed to be poofier.
Oh, you're totally right. We could add some wiring.
I think it'll be fine if I just wear a firm tutu underneath. I have one at home.
Okay, cool. Want to try the cape on with it?
Sure.
Yeah, she does!
No way. You used embossed fabric for the lining? So cool.
The only thing I'm not too keen on is that it's a bit thick, so you can't get those nice windblown shots.
I was thinking that, but if we use a multiple shot setting while moving, the cape will look like it's waving and the heavier fabric could add some nice dimension to the photo.
She sounds so cool when she gets all serious about cosplay. I want to talk like a pro, too.
Does yours fit well, Kitagawa?
Uh, um, mm-hmm.
Yeah. Well, this part's kind of tight, but, like, looks hot, so...
It's fetch! And I'm digging these gold thingies up here. Mega fetch!
And this flowy part flows! Super-duper mega fetch!
Careful there. Don't hurt yourself.
Thanks. I'm glad you like it.
Kitagawa, I think we should do your makeup and see how it looks with the wig. Can I help you pin your hair up?
Totes-ma-goats!
Marin Kitagawa, is this the only shade of foundation that you own?
Yeah, why?
Some wigs look better on different skin tones. A lighter shade with that one will look more realistic.
Color-correcting concealers can help modify tones, too.
A blue one will lighten your skin for Black Lobelia. You have one? If not, then you can use mine for the shoot.
Are you serious? That'd be so awesome!
We can change your eye shape with this.
Wait, what?
It's cosplay tape. Inui swears by it, so I got some.
Black Lobelia has a distinct eye shape. I wasn't sure we could emulate it with just false lashes, and I wanted to see how it worked.
Nice! I'm down!
Take the corner of the eye and lift up diagonally.
Did that work?
Feels weird.
Use bobby pins to keep the face tape and wig cap in place.
Should I shave my eyebrows or what?
No, your eyebrows should be even this time, so you can leave them.
Okay, you seriously shaved your eyebrows off.
And that's done.
Yeah. Looks great.
For real? Give me a mirror. I want to see.
Sure. Here you go.
Holy crap!
My face has never looked like this in my entire life!
This is nuts!
Is that really me?
Have I been Black Lobelia this whole time?
Nope, just you.
The wig's a great color.
Where is it from?
A place called Swallowtail.
They do great work.
You know, I'm not even gonna ask.
I'm so freakin' hyped right now!
Our group cosplay is gonna be so sweet!
Our group cosplay was gonna be so sweet.
Random acts of monsooning are common around this time of year.
It sucks, but at least the gloomy lighting will look good in pics.
It makes everything so depressing, but I guess you're right.
That corset is amazing.
For real, I've always loved Black Lobelia's outfit.
Oh my gosh, same!
Corsets are my jam in general. I love them so much!
I love that it looks like it's part of the dress, and that it's frilly and gothic!
Ever since I was little, I've loved how different Neon and Black Lobelia's characters are, you know?
I cannot tell you what a dream come true this is!
For sure.
Actually, I have a teeny tiny request.
What is it?
I was, um, wondering if maybe we could get a picture, like, together.
Okay. I mean, it's whatever.
Are you serious? Oh my gosh, you're the best!
I can't handle this right now! Thank you so much!
Would it be okay if I posted it?
If you want, but your makeup's a little runny.
Shinju's running crazy late.
It usually doesn't take her this long to get ready.
Gojow's not back yet, either.
Oh my god! I'm getting so many likes!
No one ever likes my photos that much!
Juju, you're a social media angel!
You could do it if you stopped posting pictures of everything you eat.
That fried rice with the whole kitchen sink in it was a bit much.
Oh yeah! I made that!
You're not serious.
Look at all these comments!
This one says,
Wow, Juju actually exists!
Of course I exist! What the heck?
When you never go to live events, people start to wonder!
Hey, you guys. Sorry for the wait.
Yeah, what took you so long?
No way.
Inui? Can you hear me?
Inui, what's wrong?
Hey, wake up!
I can't believe I did that.
I'm the one who wanted to go and then I ended up fainting like a loser.
It's totally cool, Juju.
Shinjiu and I still went and checked it all out.
Yeah, and I took pictures so we can look at them together when we get home.
Thank you.
You were worse off than I realized.
I'm so sorry. I should have noticed.
Well, I feel much better now.
Awesome. So are we ready to call it a day?
I think so.
Okay, cool.
I'm meeting up with Noah and some friends, so I'm gonna bounce for now.
We figured we'd hype ourselves up for finals with some karaoke!
Or you could just study.
Later days, you guys!
See you.
We should probably head out, too.
I've never been to Shin Misato before.
Would you mind if I looked at the shops by the station first?
You do you.
I'll just see you at home, then.
Don't be too late.
Okay.
So, um...
Iha, what's up?
Did you have any more questions about the camera before we go?
Oh, no, thank you.
I apologize in advance if I'm wrong, but...
I kind of feel like...
I don't know.
Maybe you might be interested in cosplay after all.
When we were at lunch the other day, I wondered if it was too hard to admit it in front of your sister.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Please forget I mentioned it.
I'll leave you alone.
Oh, wait.
I would like to try it, actually.
There is one.
A character that I love.
I thought maybe someday.
Maureen was right, you know?
I see how much fun my sister has cosplaying, and it's hard watching from the sidelines.
Then why?
I can't.
It's complicated.
Thing is, I wouldn't be a good fit at all.
My sister might, but I'm not cute like her.
And my body type's all wrong.
I'm basically different from this character in every way.
I'd look so ridiculous if I dressed up like that.
It would feel like I was being insulting.
That's why I never tried.
And, well, that end, if I ever did a horrible cosplay, I know I would embarrass my sister.
And I wouldn't be able to handle it if she hated me.
Plus, I'm too scared.
That's confusing to me.
When I was at the live event, I saw so many people enjoying cosplay for the first time.
And I remember thinking that the best thing about cosplay is that you can become anything you want.
So I say, if you're curious about it at all, you should try it.
And I'll help you.
Also, I've seen how much your sister loves you.
And I don't think she would ever judge you, Inui.
Thank you, Kojo.
That means a lot.
I would really appreciate your help.
Great.
Then let's do it.
So tell me, what series do you want to cosplay from?
Actually, I hope you don't mind.
My character is also from Flower Princess Blaze.
Really?
That's cool.
I wonder which one it is.
She said it was someone totally different from her, so maybe it's the heroine.
Mirai!
Okay, don't laugh.
I've always wanted to try cosplaying so much.
Wait, you mean the brother?
I've always looked up to him for so many reasons.
He's strong, he's cool.
And whenever his little sister Mirai is in trouble, he's the first one to step up and help her.
I think he's my favorite because he reminds me so much of my sister.
I see.
You know, I bet you could be part of the Blaze cosplay group with the others.
I'm sure they'd both be thrilled to have you.
Oh, that would be fun.
But could you keep it a secret until the day of?
Since it's my first time, I'm a little embarrassed.
Of course.
So, um, do you really think I can pull it off?
Yeah, why not?
Because I, um, I have a hard time finding clothes that can fit me right on top.
Yeah, those might be hard to work around.
Also, I only have my allowance so I don't have a lot of money to spend.
That's right, I forgot.
She's still in middle school.
She looks so much older, but she can't even work yet.
That's gonna be rough.
Materials cost a lot.
What am I thinking?
It's fine.
Cosplay doesn't have to be expensive.
It's all about creativity and imagination.
Everyone should be able to do it, even with limited funds.
There has to be a way I can do this for her.
Think, dummy, think.
If that sounds too difficult, please don't worry about it.
No.
I'll figure it out.
Don't worry.
Let's start with the outfit first.
Okay.
We can easily use this uniform for the base.
Is this your uniform, Gojo?
Yeah.
I thought about it, and I remembered watching Flower Princess Blaze
and thinking the uniform Soma and Sakuya were wearing
looked a lot like the one from my school.
You're right, it totally does.
You're sure it's okay if I borrow it?
Yeah.
I don't know if it'll fit you as is, but...
Let's see.
It's a good thing Kitakawa wasn't the one wanting to cosplay Soma.
Dude, these are huge on me.
There's no way she'd fit into my uniform.
Gojo, it works!
I'm wearing it!
Great!
How's it...
I'm so sorry about the buttons.
I'll pay for it.
You knew it, please!
Cover up!
I'm so sorry, Gojo.
It's fine.
I'll have these sewn on in no time.
It seemed to be around the right size, though.
I'll just hem it a bit for you.
Yeah.
He wears his sleeves rolled up, so the length was great.
My main concern is your bo...
Body.
And what we can do to help make it look more like a guy's.
Right.
At this point, she's just wearing a guy's uniform.
That doesn't feel much like cosplay.
I have to find a way to make her chest less noticeable, and her physique look more like a boy's.
I never had this issue with Hina dolls.
Of course, they're all wearing kimonos, so no buttons.
Kimono!
That's it!
Let's try a sarashi wrap.
We can use it to give you a straighter shape.
It'll help with the illusion of being a male character.
What do you think?
Want to try it?
Sounds good to me.
Now that I think of it,
Kitagawa wore two of those padded bra things for Shizuku-tan.
These cosplayers are willing to change their face, body, or entire appearance
just for the sake of looking like a character.
But...
It's the ultimate form of love!
I love her so much, I want to be her!
I think I understand why now.
It's because they love these characters so much.
My stomach doesn't stand out as much anymore.
But my chest is still there.
Oh, is it?
Actually, the shirt is highlighting your curves,
so you are still looking a bit girlish.
Let's alter the shoulders to be squarer.
Soma is really athletic, so that would make him look stronger, too.
Good idea!
Okay, perfect.
That should help a bit.
But her chest is still a problem.
How did those girls dressed as guys at the event handle it?
A bee holder?
What is that?
What?
It really flattens it that much?
Look, they have my size, too!
Okay, but I bet that's gonna be expensive.
Or maybe it won't!
No way!
Inui, we can make a man out of you without breaking the bank!
Yay!
I'll buy it right now!
All that's left is the wig!
I'd like to get it next time I'm out shopping.
So, would it be okay if I measured your head?
Of course you can!
Okay, set up straight.
And keep looking for...
Word!
I'm so sorry!
I promise I didn't mean to do that!
No, it's totally okay!
I'm sorry!
Let's not talk about it!
Thanks for coming out here.
I know it's a bit of a hike for you.
I don't mind.
Come look!
I got your wig!
Since you want your cosplay to be a surprise,
I thought we should cut it ourselves.
Wow!
He's never cut a wig and he's not hesitating at all!
It's kind of nerve-wracking.
I'm freaking out a little bit.
I don't want to mess it up.
Huh?
No!
It's fine!
I'm just so relieved that you feel that way sometimes, too.
I definitely do.
But you make the most incredible outfits!
How could someone so talented ever be insecure?
Are you kidding?
There's so much I can't do.
I'm still trying to figure it all out.
Do you really mean that?
Yeah.
I actually wish I could be more like this classmate I look up to.
She's always so positive.
Everyone who meets her loves her.
She's strong and fearless and says whatever's on her mind.
I always thought her life must be so easy.
There was no way she had problems like me.
But then...
One thing led to another,
and I ended up spending a lot of time with her.
And I realized...
She also had things she wanted to do but couldn't.
And things didn't always go her way.
She even messed up at times.
She has the same issues I do.
But she always looks happy.
And sometimes she's even kind of cute.
Huh!
Hold on!
Did I say cute?
If I did, I swear I didn't mean it like that!
Anyway, uh, what?
Did you say something?
I forgot what I was talking about.
Oh, yeah.
My point was,
we don't always know how someone really feels.
But, well, we all have struggles.
Anyway, haircuts!
We all have struggles.
Even her?
I never thought about it that way.
Okay, let's do your makeup.
I found everything you need at the 100 yen shop.
I got this entire bag for under 10,000.
Wow, thank you so much!
Looks good.
Let's do your eyes next.
To make your eyes look a little more masculine,
we'll extend the eyeliner a bit further than normal.
And the last thing we'll do is adjust the wig.
Oh, there he is.
Oh.
Shinja?
I, um, I, um, I wanted to, I guess, just try, sort of try cosplaying?
No way!
I just, I can't believe it!
You look amazing!
Oh my gosh!
Seriously, she's been cramped!
I couldn't tell who you were,
but I swear, I thought I was staring at the look of the look of the look.
It was absolutely blowing my mind!
Just so good.
I mean it.
Perfect.
I'm so impressed.
Do you like it?
Yes.
So, question.
What'd you do with your yabos?
They're like M.I.A.
I strapped them down with a compression band and a sabashi wrap.
And Gojo sewed in some shoulder pads for me.
You still have a girl face!
Girl face?
You've got like this powerful presence of a dude,
but your face still looks so girly!
The contrast is so cool, and I seriously can't with you!
Oh my gosh, Shinju, can we take a few selfies together?
Pretty, please?
Sure.
Okay, cute!
One more, and this time...
I think we should get started before our time runs out.
That's right!
I forgot we're paying air relief!
Shinju, can you get the camera?
Yep, on it!
That camera is really not cheap!
We're crying out loud, you guys!
It's fine, you guys!
Yeah, it's fine.
Coupè s belle
Thank you.